localvigyapan.com 2011-12-03

# Local Vigyapan Privacy Policy

LocalVigyapan.com's privacy policy describes how LocalVigyapan.com (we) handle your personal information. We collect, use, and share personal information to help the website ("LocalVigyapan.com") work and to keep it safe (details below). 

**Collection.** Information posted on LocalVigyapan.com may be publicly available. when you choose to provide us with personal information, you are agreeing to the transfer and storage of your information on LocalVigyapan.com servers. We collect and store the following personal information:   
email address, physical contact information, and (depending on the service used) sometimes financial information;   
computer sign-on data, statistics on page views, traffic to and from LocalVigyapan.com, Ad data (all through cookies - you can take steps to disable the cookies on your browser although this is likely to affect your ability to use the site), web server cookie stored on your hard drive, the type of computer you use, type of web browser you use;   
other information, including users Internet Protocol address assigned to the computer which you use and standard web log information.

**Use.** We use users' personal information to:   
provide our services;   
resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems;   
encourage safe trading and enforce our policies;   
customize users' experience, measure interest in our services, and inform users about services and updates;   
communicate marketing and promotional offers to you;  
Do other things for users as described when we collect the information. 

**Disclosure.**  
All information contained by LocalVigyapan.com is treated as strictly confidential and LocalVigyapan.com does not and will not disclose or share such confidential information to / with any external organization.  
The users privacy is very important to us. We do not and shall not at any point in time, either sell or rent users personal information to third parties without users explicit consent.  
We may be required from time to time to disclose users personal information to Governmental or law enforcing agencies or our regulators, but we will only do so under proper authority.  
LocalVigyapan.com also reserves the right to make use of the personal information in any investigation or judicial process relating to fraud on account of such transactions during the period LocalVigyapan.com retains such information.  
We may also disclose personal information to enforce our policies, respond to claims that a posting or other content violates other's rights, or protects any one's rights, property or safety.  
We may also share personal information with:  
\- Corporate affiliates who help detect or prevent potentially illegal acts and provide joint services (Our corporate affiliates will market only to users who ask them to).  
\- Service providers who help with our business operations.

**Using Information from LocalVigyapan.com:** You may use personal information gathered from LocalVigyapan.com only to follow up with another user about a specific posting, not to send spam/ phishing or collect personal information from someone who hasn't agreed to that. If any user is found spamming / phishing on or through our website, LocalVigyapan.com may take appropriate legal action to safeguard interests of the website and users. 

**Access, Modification, and Deletion:** You can see, modify or erase your personal information by reviewing your posting or account status page. Contact customer support at [support@localvigyapan.com](mailto:support@localvigyapan.com) to review any personal information we store that is not available on LocalVigyapan.com. There may be a charge associated with such requests but these will not exceed the amounts permitted by law. We delete personal information when we no longer need it for the purposes we described earlier. We retain personal information as permitted by law to resolve disputes, enforce our policies; and prevent bad guys from coming back.

**Data Security:** We use a number of mechanisms (encryption, passwords, and physical security) to protect the security and integrity of your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be completely secure. So while we strive to protect such information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once any personal information comes into our possession, we will take reasonable steps to protect that information from misuse and loss and from unauthorized access, modification or disclosure.

**General:** We may update, upgrade, modify (partially &/or fully) this policy at any time, with updates taking effect when you next post or after 30 days, whichever is sooner. If we or our corporate affiliates are involved in a merger or acquisition, we may share personal information with another company, but this policy will continue to apply. Send questions about this policy to privacy at LocalVigyapan.com.
